Eldo Martadjaya, B.Sc.

Full-stack Web Developer



PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Nationality: Indonesia (May need sponsored working visa in your country). Having 10+ years of web development experience locally and abroad. I have been trained in systems design, software development, Website development, project management, systems security, maintenance. -JavaScript, Node. JS, React. JS, Drupal, Wordpress, Joomla, HTML5, PHP, Laravel Web Development Project Management, cPanel, Gulp/Git/VSC, OOP, User Experience, Adobe Photoshop, Corporate Website, Web Content Production, GitHub, Git Bash/VSC, Agile/Scrum, Webmaster Services, SEO, E-Commerce Optimization, Social Media Marketing, Web Administration





+62 878 - 8826 - 2739



eldoma@gmail.com



eldoma.github.io/resume



BSD, Serpong, West of Jakarta, Indonesia

Education

DEGREE NAME // MAJOR
(Almost Finished)
University of Technology,
Sydney, Master of
Computing Science,
1999-2002

DEGREE NAME // MAJOR BINUS University, Jakarta // Bachelor of Science in Information Systems, 1993-1997. GPA 3.08/4

Expertise

- CMS: Drupal, Wordpress, Laravel, HTML5
- PHP, node.js
- Web Content Management
- Internet Strategy
- Web Projects
- E-Commerce Development
- Webmaster Services

WORK EXPERIENCE

Webmaster/Developer for several client companies Self Employed | Jakarta | Feb 2014 - Present

- Serves as the Webmaster, Full-Stack Web Developer for several Client companies and as technology advisor.Manages the clients official websites and social media presence.
- Create new ideas and maintain campaigns, and measuring how effective those ideas are. Monitor progress using analytic tools, and answer directly to social media inquiries, all while using the client companies' voice and guidelines.
- Support the development of digital campaigns for Client companies online outreach activities by creating digital campaigns, multimedia contents, and infographics.
- Work with other Sections and Departments to coordinate their campaigns with other initiatives to fit in to the overall goals of the clients' organisation.

Websites made and maintained:

cryoisotank.com, yanwo.asia,pontidelights.com,maxxelli.net, broadbandhk.com

bestbuysworld.com, cinema-chair.com, kursisekolah.my.id, penyet.pontidelights.com, cryogenic.cryoisotank.com, ensurgas.cryoisotank.com, dalmacapital.com, siigas.com, heliumindonesia.com,

Website Development Project Manager

links full at a deformanint in condensace and

Twinova Pty Ltd. | Suzhou, China | Oct 2014 - Jul 2017 - As Web developer to provide of multiple website projects for company and clients such as online meeting, presentation, testing and commissioning.

- Developing and collaboration with programmer to provide of static and dynamic website content for the company and use of several tools like; Photoshop, PHP/ Drupal / Wordpress / Joomla coding script.
- Developing customized commercial websites on PHP & several CMS using Agile/Scrum Methodology, web design and internet content development

Publication

E.M (1997) Analysis & Design of System Information Inventory & Marketing at PT AMM , *BINUS University Theses*E.M (2018) DOM Frontend Javascript:
ES6+Node.JS+NPM+HTML5+CSS+Webpack+NPM on Git Bash & Github

Continued:

Web Researcher / Content Developer

Houghton Richards | Jakarta (online) | March 2017 - Present Apr 2014-Jun 2015

Translations, Website content development & Troubleshooting. Reporting directly to Chief Development Officer. Houghton Richards is Australia's Leading Domain Brokerage House.

Research Team Leader & Quality Assurance

PreScouter, Inc. | Jakarta (online) - Chicago | Mar 2013-Feb 2015

Marketing Analyst Research Team member and Leader, QA. Reporting directly to Marketing Analyst GM. PreScouter is a technology-enabled service that allows corporate R&D labs to outsource tasks to subject matter experts.

Webmaster and Support Officer at PT Surya Indotim Imex, sister company of

Geoservices (Ltd.) | Jakarta | Apr 2011-Mar 2013

Reporting to the Business Development Manager:

- Website design and development using HTML5+CSS+Wordpress & Joomla.
- Managing and contributing to the execution of PT SII strategy including market plan development, competitor and customer assessment, pricing and demand analysis, regulatory, political and policy assessment.
- Work with market development, product management, EPC and market communications to develop targeted product offerings.
- Provide information to business development and market communications teams to assist in the promotion of the organization's goods and/or services.
- Actively manage all customer and sales activities for the PT SII business to be the central source of all specialty and standard gas market development support for Indonesia.
- Local representative lead for external facing activities, including customer engagement, transaction execution and regulatory affairs.
- Webmaster and Product Support Developing commercial activities





Sekolah Tinggi Manajemen Informatika dan Komputer (STMIK)

Bina Nusantara

Jln. K.H. Syahdan - Kemanggisan, Palmerah - Jakarta Barat (11480) Fax 5300244, Telepon 5345830 - 5322160

FM-BINUS-AA-FPU-86/kV

** TRANSCRIPT OF ACADEMIC RECORD **

(Undergraduate Program)

This is to certify that:

N a m e : ELDO MARTADJAJA Student Number : 0101930299 Registration Number : 933333716650276 Place & Date of Birth : Jakarta, JULY 11, 1975

as finished his Undergraduate Program in Management Information System with the tollowing results:

40. SUBJECTS	CREDIT	GRADE		No.	SUBJECTS	CREDIT	GRADE	
11. Accounting-1 12. Introduction to EDP 13. Logic & Algorithms 14. Ethics 15. English-1 16. Cobol-1 Programming 16. Linear Algebra 18. Discrete Mathematics 19. General Management 19. Accounting-2 11. Data Structures 12. Program Design Method 15. English-2 14. Cobol-2 Programming 15. Calculus 16. Management Information System 17. Database Concept 18. Pancasila 19. Digital Technique 19. Package Program 10. Cobol-3 Programming 11. Systo Analysis 11. Theory of National Defense 12. Linear Programming 12. Systo Analysis 15. Theory of National Defense 16. Introduction to Economics 17. Computer Organization 18. Data Communication 19. Bata Communication 19. Statistics & Probability Theory-2 19. Systo Design 19. Compilation Technique 19. Changuage 19. Research Methodology 19. Manerical Method	22422222244224224224222422242224222		48866668644886664484666686866666866	37. 38. 39. 40. 41. 42. 43. 44. 45. 46. 47. 50. 51. 52. 53.	System Information Project Organizational Behaviour Graph System Basic Humanity Simulation Technique Advanced Calculus Papers Production Management Operational Research EDP Management Computer Audit Derating System Basic Social Science Leadership Seminar Software Engineering Thesis Job Training	42422442222222222222222222222222222222	A A B C C A A B A C B B B A B A	16 6 4 8 16 8 6 8 4 6 2 2 6 8 12 6 8
Total	= 148 c	redits			Cummulative GPA = 3,02			

Brade: 4: 85-100; B: 75-84; C: 65-74; D: 50-64; P: Passed

Title of Thesis: Analysis and Design of System Information Purchasing Inventory and Marketing at

Job Training at : PT. LANGGENG GITAMUSIKAL Period : November 1996 - January 1997

Jakarta, October 12, 1997

STMIK BINA NUSANTARA

Signed

Ir. Th. Widia S., Mh Principal

Ir. Th. Widia S., M. Principal

Attested by,